

AHMAD **AL_SMADI**

About Me wy goar is to join a reputable organization where I can leverage my skills, gain valuable experience, and contribute meaningfully to the company's objectives. As a Jordanian, I am particularly interested in opportunities within Malaysian universities, especially in roles related to student recruitment.



+49 1521 4300501



Smaqiingermany@yanoo.com



Frankturter Hing, 8080/ München

LANGUAGE

- Arabic
- English
- Malay (basic)

EXPERTISE

- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Digital Marketing
- Negotiation
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership

WORK EXPERIENCE

Middle East service

Marketing Manager

2020 - 2023

Malaysian Universities

Student Recruiter

2016 - 2020

MOBILY COMPANY

Marketing Employee

02015 - 2016

self-employed

Education Advisor

2013-2022

EDUCATION

University sultan Zainal Abidin

Ph.D. Business and management

2021- Expected study

Al madinah International University

Master of information communication technology

2015-2017

AL Balga Applied University

Bachelor in computer science

2009 - 2012

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Strong command of communication in different languages
- Strong decision maker and complex problem solver
- Persuasive. Critical innovative thinker and fast learner
- Excellent IT skills, MS Office, Social media
- Advanced knowledge of searching on the internet
- Excellent in quantitative and qualitative research methods
- Data analysis using SPSS
- Able to communicate with a wide range of audience
- Able to prioritize workload and excellent management skills
- Self-awareness, Purposeful, focused, reflective and honest
- Pro-activity, Resourceful, flexible, self-starter, initiative

I KAINING COURSE

TRAINING OF TRAINERS (TOT) IN KUALA LUMPUR

ICDL - International Computer Driving Licence

Communication Skills Training Course in Kuala Lumpur

Body language in Kuala Lumpur

English skills in Kuala Lumpur

Human Resource Management in Kuala Lumpur

Professional Marketing in Kuala Lumpur

Confidence itself in Kuala Lumpur

JUB TAKGET

My goal is to become associated with a company where I can utilize my skills and gain further experience while enhancing the company's productivity and reputation. Personally, I have the drive and determination to consistently achieve success as a leader in all of the organizations